Guide to the Dial/Scofield Thayer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile, 4.8; (12 boxes)
  - Box 3, folder 104 (Box 85, Folder 2193)
  - Box 3, folder 105 (Box 85, Folder 2194)
  - Box 3, folder 106 (Box 85, Folder 2195)
  - Box 3, folder 107 (Box 85, Folder 2196)
  - Box 3, folder 108 (Box 85, Folder 2197)
  - Box 3, folder 109 (Box 85, Folder 2198)
  - Box 3, folder 110 (Box 85, Folder 2199)
  - Box 3, folder 111 (Box 85, Folder 2200)
  - Box 3, folder 112 (Box 85, Folder 2201)
  - Box 3, folder 113 (Box 85, Folder 2202)
  - Box 3, folder 114 (Box 85, Folder 2203)
  - Box 3, folder 115 (Box 85, Folder 2204)
  - Box 3, folder 116 (Box 85, Folder 2205)
  - Box 3, folder 117 (Box 85, Folder 2206)
  - Box 3, folder 118 (Box 85, Folder 2207)
  - Box 3, folder 119 (Box 85, Folder 2208)
  - Box 3, folder 120 (Box 85, Folder 2209)
  - Box 3, folder 121 (Box 85, Folder 2210)
  - Box 4, folder 122 (Box 85, Folder 2211)
  - Box 4, folder 123 (Box 85, Folder 2212)
  - Box 4, folder 124 (Box 85, Folder 2213)
  - Box 4, folder 125 (Box 85, Folder 2214)
  - Box 4, folder 126 (Box 85, Folder 2215)
  - Box 4, folder 127 (Box 85, Folder 2216)
  - Box 4, folder 128 (Box 85, Folder 2217)
  - Box 4, folder 129 (Box 85, Folder 2218)
  - Box 4, folder 130 (Box 85, Folder 2219)
  - Box 4, folder 131 (Box 85, Folder 2220)
  - Box 4, folder 132 (Box 85, Folder 2221)
  - Box 4, folder 133 (Box 85, Folder 2222)
  - Box 4, folder 134 (Box 85, Folder 2223)
  - Box 4, folder 135 (Box 85, Folder 2224)
  - Box 4, folder 136 (Box 85, Folder 2225)
  - Box 4, folder 137 (Box 85, Folder 2226)
  - Box 4, folder 138 (Box 85, Folder 2227)
  - Box 4, folder 139 (Box 85, Folder 2228)
  - Box 4, folder 140 (Box 85, Folder 2229)
  - Box 4, folder 141 (Box 85, Folder 2230)
  - Box 4, folder 142 (Box 85, Folder 2231)
  - Box 4, folder 143 (Box 85, Folder 2232)
  - Box 4, folder 144 (Box 85, Folder 2233)
  - Box 4, folder 145 (Box 85, Folder 2234)
  - Box 4, folder 146 (Box 85, Folder 2235)
  - Box 4, folder 147 (Box 85, Folder 2236)
  - Box 4, folder 148 (Box 85, Folder 2237)
  - Box 4, folder 149 (Box 85, Folder 2238)
  - Box 4, folder 150 (Box 85, Folder 2239)
  - Box 4, folder 151 (Box 85, Folder 2240)
  - Box 4, folder 152 (Box 85, Folder 2241)
  - Box 4, folder 153 (Box 85, Folder 2242)
  - Box 4, folder 154 (Box 85, Folder 2243)
  - Box 4, folder 155 (Box 85, Folder 2244)
  - Box 4, folder 156 (Box 85, Folder 2245)
  - Box 4, folder 157 (Box 85, Folder 2246)
  - Box 4, folder 158 (Box 85, Folder 2247)
  - Box 4, folder 160 (Box 85, Folder 2248)
  - Box 5, folder 161 (Box 85, Folder 2249)
  - Box 5, folder 162 (Box 85, Folder 2250)
  - Box 5, folder 163 (Box 85, Folder 2251)
  - Box 5, folder 164 (Box 85, Folder 2252)
  - Box 5, folder 165 (Box 85, Folder 2253)
  - Box 5, folder 166 (Box 85, Folder 2254)
  - Box 5, folder 167 (Box 85, Folder 2255)
  - Box 5, folder 168 (Box 85, Folder 2256)
  - Box 5, folder 169 (Box 85, Folder 2257)
  - Box 5, folder 170 (Box 85, Folder 2258)
  - Box 5, folder 171 (Box 85, Folder 2259)
  - Box 5, folder 172 (Box 85, Folder 2260)
  - Box 5, folder 173 (Box 85, Folder 2261)
  - Box 5, folder 174 (Box 85, Folder 2262)
  - Box 5, folder 175 (Box 85, Folder 2263)
  - Box 5, folder 176 (Box 85, Folder 2264)
  - Box 5, folder 177 (Box 85, Folder 2265)
  - Box 5, folder 178 (Box 85, Folder 2266)
  - Box 5, folder 179 (Box 85, Folder 2267)
  - Box 5, folder 180 (Box 86, Folder 2268)
  - Box 5, folder 181 (Box 86, Folder 2269)
  - Box 5, folder 182 (Box 86, Folder 2270)
  - Box 5, folder 183 (Box 86, Folder 2271)
  - Box 5, folder 184 (Box 86, Folder 2272)
  - Box 5, folder 185 (Box 86, Folder 2273)
  - Box 5, folder 186 (Box 86, Folder 2274)
  - Box 5, folder 187 (Box 86, Folder 2275)
  - Box 5, folder 188 (Box 86, Folder 2276)
  - Box 5, folder 189 (Box 86, Folder 2277)
  - Box 5, folder 190 (Box 86, Folder 2278)
  - Box 5, folder 191 (Box 86, Folder 2279)
  - Box 5, folder 192 (Box 86, Folder 2280)
  - Box 5, folder 193 (Box 86, Folder 2281)
  - Box 5, folder 194 (Box 86, Folder 2282)
  - Box 5, folder 195 (Box 86, Folder 2283)
  - Box 5, folder 196 (Box 86, Folder 2284)
  - Box 5, folder 197 (Box 86, Folder 2285)
  - Box 5, folder 198 (Box 86, Folder 2286)
  - Box 5, folder 199 (Box 86, Folder 2287)
  - Box 6, folder 200 (Box 86, Folder 2288)
  - Box 6, folder 201 (Box 86, Folder 2289)
  - Box 6, folder 202 (Box 86, Folder 2290)
  - Box 6, folder 203 (Box 86, Folder 2291)
  - Box 6, folder 204 (Box 86, Folder 2292)
  - Box 6, folder 205 (Box 86, Folder 2293)
  - Box 6, folder 206 (Box 86, Folder 2294)
  - Box 6, folder 207 (Box 86, Folder 2295)
  - Box 6, folder 208 (Box 86, Folder 2296)
  - Box 6, folder 209 (Box 86, Folder 2297)
  - Box 6, folder 210 (Box 86, Folder 2298)
  - Box 6, folder 211 (Box 86, Folder 2299)
  - Box 6, folder 212 (Box 86, Folder 2300)
  - Box 6, folder 213 (Box 86, Folder 2301)
  - Box 6, folder 214 (Box 86, Folder 2302)
  - Box 6, folder 215 (Box 86, Folder 2303)
  - Box 6, folder 216 (Box 86, Folder 2304)
  - Box 6, folder 217 (Box 86, Folder 2305)
  - Box 6, folder 218 (Box 86, Folder 2306)
  - Box 6, folder 219 (Box 86, Folder 2307)
  - Box 6, folder 220 (Box 86, Folder 2308)
  - Box 6, folder 221 (Box 86, Folder 2309)
  - Box 6, folder 222 (Box 86, Folder 2310)
  - Box 6, folder 223 (Box 86, Folder 2311)
  - Box 6, folder 224 (Box 86, Folder 2312)
  - Box 6, folder 225 (Box 86, Folder 2313)
  - Box 6, folder 226 (Box 86, Folder 2314)
  - Box 6, folder 227 (Box 86, Folder 2315)
  - Box 6, folder 228 (Box 86, Folder 2316)
  - Box 6, folder 229 (Box 86, Folder 2317)
  - Box 6, folder 230 (Box 86, Folder 2318)
  - Box 6, folder 231 (Box 86, Folder 2319)
  - Box 6, folder 232 (Box 86, Folder 2320)
  - Box 6, folder 233 (Box 86, Folder 2321)
  - Box 6, folder 234 (Box 86, Folder 2322)
  - Box 6, folder 235 (Box 86, Folder 2323)
  - Box 6, folder 236 (Box 86, Folder 2324)
  - Box 6, folder 237 (Box 86, Folder 2325)
  - Box 6, folder 238 (Box 86, Folder 2326)
  - Box 6, folder 239 (Box 86, Folder 2327)
  - Box 7, folder 240 (Box 86, Folder 2328)
  - Box 7, folder 241 (Box 86, Folder 2329)
  - Box 7, folder 242 (Box 86, Folder 2330)
  - Box 7, folder 243 (Box 86, Folder 2331)
  - Box 7, folder 245 (Box 86, Folder 2332)
  - Box 7, folder 246 (Box 86, Folder 2333)
  - Box 7, folder 247 (Box 86, Folder 2334)
  - Box 7, folder 248 (Box 86, Folder 2335)
  - Box 7, folder 249 (Box 86, Folder 2336)
  - Box 7, folder 250 (Box 86, Folder 2337)
  - Box 7, folder 251 (Box 86, Folder 2338)
  - Box 7, folder 252 (Box 86, Folder 2339)
  - Box 7, folder 253 (Box 87, Folder 2340)
  - Box 7, folder 254 (Box 87, Folder 2341)
  - Box 7, folder 255 (Box 87, Folder 2342)
  - Box 7, folder 256 (Box 87, Folder 2343)
  - Box 7, folder 257 (Box 87, Folder 2344)
  - Box 7, folder 258 (Box 87, Folder 2345)
  - Box 7, folder 259 (Box 87, Folder 2346)
  - Box 7, folder 260 (Box 87, Folder 2347)
  - Box 7, folder 261 (Box 87, Folder 2348)
  - Box 7, folder 262 (Box 87, Folder 2349)
  - Box 7, folder 263 (Box 87, Folder 2350)
  - Box 7, folder 264 (Box 87, Folder 2351)
  - Box 7, folder 265 (Box 87, Folder 2352)
  - Box 7, folder 266 (Box 87, Folder 2353)
  - Box 7, folder 267 (Box 87, Folder 2354)
  - Box 7, folder 268 (Box 87, Folder 2355)
  - Box 7, folder 269 (Box 87, Folder 2356)
  - Box 7, folder 270 (Box 87, Folder 2357)
  - Box 7, folder 271 (Box 87, Folder 2358)
  - Box 7, folder 272 (Box 87, Folder 2359)
  - Box 7, folder 273 (Box 87, Folder 2360)
  - Box 7, folder 274 (Box 87, Folder 2361)
  - Box 7, folder 275 (Box 87, Folder 2362)
  - Box 7, folder 276 (Box 87, Folder 2363)
  - Box 7, folder 277 (Box 87, Folder 2364)
  - Box 7, folder 278 (Box 87, Folder 2365)
  - Box 7, folder 279 (Box 87, Folder 2366)
  - Box 7, folder 280 (Box 87, Folder 2367)
  - Box 7, folder 281 (Box 87, Folder 2368)
  - Box 8, folder 282 (Box 87, Folder 2369)
  - Box 8, folder 283 (Box 87, Folder 2370)
  - Box 8, folder 284 (Box 87, Folder 2371)
  - Box 8, folder 285 (Box 87, Folder 2372)
  - Box 8, folder 286 (Box 87, Folder 2373)
  - Box 8, folder 287 (Box 87, Folder 2374)
  - Box 8, folder 288 (Box 87, Folder 2375)
  - Box 8, folder 289 (Box 87, Folder 2376)
  - Box 8, folder 290 (Box 87, Folder 2377)
  - Box 8, folder 291 (Box 87, Folder 2378)
  - Box 8, folder 292 (Box 87, Folder 2379)
  - Box 8, folder 293 (Box 87, Folder 2380)
  - Box 8, folder 294 (Box 87, Folder 2381)
  - Box 8, folder 295 (Box 87, Folder 2382)
  - Box 8, folder 296 (Box 87, Folder 2383)
  - Box 8, folder 297 (Box 87, Folder 2384)
  - Box 8, folder 298 (Box 87, Folder 2385)
  - Box 8, folder 299 (Box 87, Folder 2386)
  - Box 8, folder 300 (Box 87, Folder 2387)
  - Box 8, folder 301 (Box 87, Folder 2388)
  - Box 8, folder 303 (Box 87, Folder 2389)
  - Box 8, folder 304 (Box 87, Folder 2390)
  - Box 9, folder 306 (Box 87, Folder 2391)
  - Box 9, folder 311 (Box 87, Folder 2392)
  - Box 9, folder 319 (Box 87, Folder 2393)
  - Box 9, folder 320 (Box 87, Folder 2394)
  - Box 9, folder 321 (Box 87, Folder 2395)
  - Box 9, folder 322 (Box 87, Folder 2396)
  - Box 9, folder 323 (Box 87, Folder 2397)
  - Box 9, folder 353 (Box 87, Folder 2398)
  - Box 9, folder 355 (Box 87, Folder 2399)
  - Box 19, folder 362 (Box 87, Folder 2400)
  - Box 19, folder 366 (Box 87, Folder 2401)
  - Box 19, folder 367 (Box 87, Folder 2402)
  - Box 19, folder 372 (Box 87, Folder 2403)
  - Box 19, folder 377 (Box 87, Folder 2404)
  - Box 19, folder 378 (Box 87, Folder 2405)
  - Box 19, folder 383 (Box 87, Folder 2406)
  - Box 19, folder 394 (Box 87, Folder 2407)
  - Box 19, folder 396 (Box 87, Folder 2408)
  - Box 20, folder 398 (Box 87, Folder 2409)
  - Box 20, folder 404 (Box 87, Folder 2410)
  - Box 20, folder 424 (Box 87, Folder 2411)
  - Box 20, folder 425 (Box 87, Folder 2412)
  - Box 20, folder 429 (Box 87, Folder 2413)
  - Box 20, folder 433 (Box 87, Folder 2414)
  - Box 20, folder 435 (Box 87, Folder 2415)
  - Box 20, folder 445 (Box 87, Folder 2416)
  - Box 21, folder 446 (Box 87, Folder 2417)
  - Box 21, folder 478 (Box 87, Folder 2418)
  - Box 21, folder 483 (Box 87, Folder 2419)
  - Box 22, folder 488 (Box 87, Folder 2420)
  - Box 22, folder 501 (Box 87, Folder 2421)
  - Box 22, folder 528 (Box 87, Folder 2422)
  - Box 22, folder 651 (Box 87, Folder 2423)
  - Box 22, folder 652 (Box 87, Folder 2424)
  - Box 26, folder 653 (Box 87, Folder 2425)
  - Box 26, folder 659 (Box 87, Folder 2426)
  - Box 26, folder 660 (Box 88, Folder 2427)
  - Box 26, folder 661 (Box 88, Folder 2428)
  - Box 26, folder 662 (Box 88, Folder 2429)
  - Box 26, folder 666 (Box 88, Folder 2430)
  - Box 26, folder 670 (Box 88, Folder 2431)
  - Box 26, folder 671 (Box 88, Folder 2432)
  - Box 26, folder 673 (Box 88, Folder 2433)
  - Box 26, folder 675 (Box 88, Folder 2434)
  - Box 26, folder 676 (Box 88, Folder 2435)
  - Box 26, folder 677 (Box 88, Folder 2436)
  - Box 26, folder 678 (Box 88, Folder 2437)
  - Box 26, folder 689 (Box 88, Folder 2438)
  - Box 27, folder 766 (Box 88, Folder 2439)
  - Box 27, folder 718 (Box 88, Folder 2440)
  - Box 27, folder 722 (Box 88, Folder 2441)
  - Box 27, folder 727 (Box 88, Folder 2442)
  - Box 27, folder 729 (Box 88, Folder 2443)
  - Box 27, folder 730 (Box 88, Folder 2444)
  - Box 28, folder 731 (Box 88, Folder 2445)
  - Box 28, folder 733 (Box 88, Folder 2446)
  - Box 28, folder 734 (Box 88, Folder 2447)
  - Box 28, folder 737 (Box 88, Folder 2448)
  - Box 28, folder 738 (Box 88, Folder 2449)
  - Box 28, folder 741 (Box 88, Folder 2450)
  - Box 28, folder 742 (Box 88, Folder 2451)
  - Box 28, folder 744 (Box 88, Folder 2452)
  - Box 28, folder 746 (Box 88, Folder 2453)
  - Box 28, folder 752 (Box 88, Folder 2454)
  - Box 28, folder 754 (Box 88, Folder 2455)
  - Box 28, folder 755 (Box 88, Folder 2456)
  - Box 28, folder 756 (Box 88, Folder 2457)
  - Box 28, folder 757 (Box 88, Folder 2458)
  - Box 28, folder 759 (Box 88, Folder 2459)
  - Box 28, folder 761 (Box 89, Folder 2460)
  - Box 28, folder 762 (Box 89, Folder 2461)
  - Box 29, folder 764 (Box 89, Folder 2462)
  - Box 29, folder 765 (Box 89, Folder 2463)
  - Box 29, folder 766 (Box 89, Folder 2464)
  - Box 29, folder 767 (Box 89, Folder 2465)
  - Box 29, folder 769 (Box 89, Folder 2466)
  - Box 29, folder 770 (Box 89, Folder 2467)
  - Box 29, folder 771 (Box 89, Folder 2468)
  - Box 29, folder 772 (Box 89, Folder 2469)
  - Box 29, folder 773 (Box 89, Folder 2470)
  - Box 29, folder 775 (Box 89, Folder 2471)
  - Box 29, folder 776 (Box 89, Folder 2472)
  - Box 30, folder 777 (Box 89, Folder 2473)
  - Box 30, folder 778 (Box 89, Folder 2474)
  - Box 30, folder 779 (Box 89, Folder 2475)
  - Box 30, folder 781 (Box 89, Folder 2476)
  - Box 30, folder 784 (Box 89, Folder 2477)
  - Box 30, folder 786 (Box 89, Folder 2478)
  - Box 30, folder 791 (Box 89, Folder 2479)
  - Box 30, folder 793 (Box 89, Folder 2480)
  - Box 30, folder 794 (Box 89, Folder 2481)
  - Box 30, folder 795 (Box 89, Folder 2482)
  - Box 30, folder 796 (Box 89, Folder 2483)
  - Box 30, folder 797 (Box 89, Folder 2484)
  - Box 30, folder 798 (Box 89, Folder 2485)
  - Box 30, folder 800 (Box 89, Folder 2486)
  - Box 30, folder 801 (Box 89, Folder 2487)
  - Box 30, folder 802 (Box 89, Folder 2488)
  - Box 30, folder 804 (Box 89, Folder 2489)
  - Box 30, folder 806 (Box 89, Folder 2490)
  - Box 30, folder 807 (Box 89, Folder 2491)
  - Box 31, folder 808 (Box 89, Folder 2492)
  - Box 31, folder 809 (Box 89, Folder 2493)
  - Box 31, folder 810 (Box 89, Folder 2494)
  - Box 31, folder 811 (Box 89, Folder 2495)
  - Box 31, folder 814 (Box 89, Folder 2496)
  - Box 31, folder 819 (Box 89, Folder 2497)
  - Box 31, folder 820 (Box 89, Folder 2498)
  - Box 31, folder 821 (Box 89, Folder 2499)
  - Box 31, folder 823 (Box 89, Folder 2500)
  - Box 31, folder 838 (Box 89, Folder 2501)
  - Box 32, folder 839 (Box 89, Folder 2502)
  - Box 32, folder 840 (Box 89, Folder 2503)
  - Box 32, folder 844 (Box 89, Folder 2504)
  - Box 32, folder 845 (Box 89, Folder 2505)
  - Box 32, folder 846 (Box 89, Folder 2506)
  - Box 32, folder 847 (Box 89, Folder 2507)
  - Box 32, folder 857 (Box 89, Folder 2508)
  - Box 32, folder 858 (Box 89, Folder 2509)
  - Box 32, folder 860 (Box 89, Folder 2510)
  - Box 32, folder 861 (Box 89, Folder 2511)
  - Box 32, folder 862 (Box 89, Folder 2512)
  - Box 32, folder 863 (Box 89, Folder 2513)
  - Box 32, folder 864 (Box 89, Folder 2514)
  - Box 32, folder 865 (Box 89, Folder 2515)
  - Box 32, folder 866 (Box 89, Folder 2516)
  - Box 32, folder 867 (Box 89, Folder 2517)
  - Box 33, folder 871 (Box 89, Folder 2518)
  - Box 33, folder 873 (Box 89, Folder 2519)
  - Box 33, folder 874 (Box 89, Folder 2520)
  - Box 33, folder 893 (Box 89, Folder 2521)
  - Box 33, folder 895 (Box 89, Folder 2522)
  - Box 33, folder 896 (Box 89, Folder 2523)
  - Box 34, folder 897 (Box 89, Folder 2524)
  - Box 34, folder 898 (Box 89, Folder 2525)
  - Box 34, folder 899 (Box 89, Folder 2526)
  - Box 34, folder 900 (Box 89, Folder 2527)
  - Box 34, folder 902 (Box 89, Folder 2528)
  - Box 34, folder 904 (Box 89, Folder 2529)
  - Box 34, folder 906 (Box 89, Folder 2530)
  - Box 34, folder 907 (Box 89, Folder 2531)
  - Box 34, folder 908 (Box 89, Folder 2532)
  - Box 34, folder 909 (Box 89, Folder 2533)
  - Box 34, folder 910 (Box 89, Folder 2534)
  - Box 34, folder 911 (Box 89, Folder 2535)
  - Box 34, folder 912 (Box 89, Folder 2536)
  - Box 34, folder 914 (Box 89, Folder 2537)
  - Box 34, folder 915 (Box 90, Folder 2538)
  - Box 34, folder 917 (Box 90, Folder 2539)
  - Box 34, folder 918 (Box 90, Folder 2540)
  - Box 34, folder 919 (Box 90, Folder 2541)
  - Box 34, folder 923 (Box 90, Folder 2542)
  - Box 34, folder 924 (Box 90, Folder 2543)
  - Box 34, folder 925 (Box 90, Folder 2544)
  - Box 34, folder 926 (Box 90, Folder 2545)
  - Box 34, folder 929 (Box 90, Folder 2546)
  - Box 34, folder 930 (Box 90, Folder 2547)
  - Box 34, folder 931 (Box 90, Folder 2548)
  - Box 34, folder 932 (Box 90, Folder 2549)
  - Box 34, folder 933 (Box 90, Folder 2550)
  - Box 34, folder 934 (Box 90, Folder 2551)
  - Box 34, folder 935 (Box 90, Folder 2552)
  - Box 34, folder 936 (Box 90, Folder 2553)
  - Box 34, folder 937 (Box 90, Folder 2554)
  - Box 34, folder 938 (Box 90, Folder 2555)
  - Box 34, folder 939 (Box 90, Folder 2556)
  - Box 34, folder 940 (Box 90, Folder 2557)
  - Box 34, folder 941 (Box 90, Folder 2558)
  - Box 34, folder 942 (Box 90, Folder 2559)
  - Box 34, folder 943 (Box 90, Folder 2560)
  - Box 34, folder 944 (Box 90, Folder 2561)
  - Box 34, folder 945 (Box 90, Folder 2562)
  - Box 34, folder 947 (Box 90, Folder 2563)
  - Box 34, folder 949 (Box 90, Folder 2564)
  - Box 34, folder 950 (Box 90, Folder 2565)
  - Box 35, folder 951 (Box 90, Folder 2566)
  - Box 35, folder 952 (Box 90, Folder 2567)
  - Box 35, folder 953 (Box 90, Folder 2568)
  - Box 35, folder 954 (Box 90, Folder 2569)
  - Box 35, folder 955 (Box 90, Folder 2570)
  - Box 35, folder 956 (Box 90, Folder 2571)
  - Box 35, folder 958 (Box 90, Folder 2572)
  - Box 35, folder 959 (Box 90, Folder 2573)
  - Box 35, folder 960 (Box 90, Folder 2574)
  - Box 35, folder 961 (Box 90, Folder 2575)
  - Box 35, folder 962 (Box 90, Folder 2576)
  - Box 35, folder 963 (Box 90, Folder 2577)
  - Box 35, folder 964 (Box 90, Folder 2578)
  - Box 35, folder 965 (Box 90, Folder 2579)
  - Box 35, folder 966 (Box 90, Folder 2580)
  - Box 35, folder 967 (Box 90, Folder 2581)
  - Box 35, folder 968 (Box 90, Folder 2582)
  - Box 35, folder 969 (Box 90, Folder 2583)
  - Box 35, folder 970 (Box 90, Folder 2584)
  - Box 35, folder 971 (Box 90, Folder 2585)
  - Box 35, folder 972 (Box 90, Folder 2586)
  - Box 35, folder 973 (Box 90, Folder 2587)
  - Box 35, folder 974 (Box 90, Folder 2588)
  - Box 35, folder 975 (Box 90, Folder 2589)
  - Box 35, folder 976 (Box 90, Folder 2590)
  - Box 35, folder 977 (Box 90, Folder 2591)
  - Box 35, folder 978 (Box 90, Folder 2592)
  - Box 35, folder 979 (Box 90, Folder 2593)
  - Box 36, folder 986 (Box 90, Folder 2594)
  - Box 36, folder 991 (Box 90, Folder 2595)
  - Box 36, folder 992 (Box 90, Folder 2596)
  - Box 36, folder 993 (Box 90, Folder 2597)
  - Box 36, folder 999 (Box 90, Folder 2598)
  - Box 36, folder 1002 (Box 90, Folder 2599)
  - Box 36, folder 1003 (Box 90, Folder 2600)
  - Box 36, folder 1004 (Box 90, Folder 2601)
  - Box 36, folder 1005 (Box 90, Folder 2602)
  - Box 36, folder 1006 (Box 90, Folder 2603)
  - Box 36, folder 1007 (Box 91, Folder 2604)
  - Box 37, folder 1013 (Box 91, Folder 2605)
  - Box 37, folder 1015 (Box 91, Folder 2606)
  - Box 37, folder 1016 (Box 91, Folder 2607)
  - Box 37, folder 1018 (Box 91, Folder 2608)
  - Box 37, folder 1019 (Box 91, Folder 2609)
  - Box 37, folder 1020 (Box 91, Folder 2610)
  - Box 37, folder 1023 (Box 91, Folder 2611)
  - Box 37, folder 1024 (Box 91, Folder 2612)
  - Box 37, folder 1026 (Box 91, Folder 2613)
  - Box 37, folder 1027 (Box 91, Folder 2614)
  - Box 37, folder 1029 (Box 91, Folder 2615)
  - Box 37, folder 1030 (Box 91, Folder 2616)
  - Box 37, folder 1031 (Box 91, Folder 2617)
  - Box 37, folder 1033 (Box 91, Folder 2618)
  - Box 37, folder 1034 (Box 91, Folder 2619)
  - Box 37, folder 1035 (Box 91, Folder 2620)
  - Box 37, folder 1036 (Box 91, Folder 2621)
  - Box 37, folder 1037 (Box 91, Folder 2622)
  - Box 37, folder 1038 (Box 91, Folder 2623)
  - Box 37, folder 1039 (Box 91, Folder 2624)
  - Box 37, folder 1042 (Box 91, Folder 2625)
  - Box 37, folder 1043 (Box 91, Folder 2626)
  - Box 37, folder 1044 (Box 91, Folder 2627)
  - Box 37, folder 1045 (Box 91, Folder 2628)
  - Box 38, folder 1047 (Box 91, Folder 2629)
  - Box 38, folder 1048 (Box 91, Folder 2630)
  - Box 38, folder 1049 (Box 91, Folder 2631)
  - Box 38, folder 1050 (Box 91, Folder 2632)
  - Box 38, folder 1051 (Box 91, Folder 2633)
  - Box 38, folder 1052 (Box 91, Folder 2634)
  - Box 38, folder 1054 (Box 91, Folder 2635)
  - Box 38, folder 1056 (Box 91, Folder 2636)
  - Box 38, folder 1058 (Box 91, Folder 2637)
  - Box 38, folder 1069 (Box 91, Folder 2638)
  - Box 38, folder 1070 (Box 91, Folder 2639)
  - Box 38, folder 1071 (Box 91, Folder 2640)
  - Box 38, folder 1072 (Box 91, Folder 2641)
  - Box 38, folder 1074 (Box 91, Folder 2642)
  - Box 38, folder 1076 (Box 91, Folder 2643)
  - Box 38, folder 1077 (Box 91, Folder 2644)
  - Box 38, folder 1081 (Box 91, Folder 2645)
  - Box 38, folder 1084 (Box 91, Folder 2646)
  - Box 38, folder 1088 (Box 91, Folder 2647)
  - Box 39, folder 1089 (Box 91, Folder 2648)
  - Box 39, folder 1090 (Box 91, Folder 2649)
  - Box 39, folder 1091 (Box 91, Folder 2650)
  - Box 39, folder 1092 (Box 91, Folder 2651)
  - Box 39, folder 1093 (Box 91, Folder 2652)
  - Box 39, folder 1094 (Box 91, Folder 2653)
  - Box 39, folder 1095 (Box 91, Folder 2654)
  - Box 39, folder 1096 (Box 91, Folder 2655)
  - Box 39, folder 1097 (Box 91, Folder 2656)
  - Box 39, folder 1098 (Box 91, Folder 2657)
  - Box 39, folder 1100 (Box 91, Folder 2658)
  - Box 39, folder 1102 (Box 91, Folder 2659)
  - Box 39, folder 1104 (Box 91, Folder 2660)
  - Box 39, folder 1105 (Box 91, Folder 2661)
  - Box 39, folder 1106 (Box 91, Folder 2662)
  - Box 39, folder 1107 (Box 91, Folder 2663)
  - Box 39, folder 1109 (Box 91, Folder 2664)
  - Box 39, folder 1110 (Box 91, Folder 2665)
  - Box 39, folder 1111 (Box 91, Folder 2666)
  - Box 39, folder 1112 (Box 91, Folder 2667)
  - Box 39, folder 1113 (Box 91, Folder 2668)
  - Box 39, folder 1114 (Box 91, Folder 2669)
  - Box 39, folder 1116 (Box 91, Folder 2670)
  - Box 40, folder 1121 (Box 91, Folder 2671)
  - Box 40, folder 1122 (Box 91, Folder 2672)
  - Box 40, folder 1123 (Box 91, Folder 2673)
  - Box 40, folder 1126 (Box 91, Folder 2674)
  - Box 40, folder 1130 (Box 91, Folder 2675)
  - Box 40, folder 1132 (Box 91, Folder 2676)
  - Box 40, folder 1133 (Box 91, Folder 2677)
  - Box 40, folder 1135 (Box 91, Folder 2678)
  - Box 40, folder 1137 (Box 91, Folder 2679)
  - Box 40, folder 1138 (Box 91, Folder 2680)
  - Box 40, folder 1139 (Box 91, Folder 2681)
  - Box 40, folder 1141 (Box 91, Folder 2682)
  - Box 40, folder 1142 (Box 91, Folder 2683)
  - Box 40, folder 1144 (Box 91, Folder 2684)
  - Box 40, folder 1145 (Box 91, Folder 2685)
  - Box 40, folder 1146 (Box 91, Folder 2686)
  - Box 40, folder 1147 (Box 91, Folder 2687)
  - Box 40, folder 1149 (Box 91, Folder 2688)
  - Box 40, folder 1151 (Box 91, Folder 2689)
  - Box 40, folder 1152 (Box 91, Folder 2690)
  - Box 41, folder 1153 (Box 91, Folder 2691)
  - Box 41, folder 1155 (Box 91, Folder 2692)
  - Box 41, folder 1156 (Box 91, Folder 2693)
  - Box 41, folder 1157 (Box 91, Folder 2694)
  - Box 41, folder 1159 (Box 91, Folder 2695)
  - Box 41, folder 1160 (Box 91, Folder 2696)
  - Box 41, folder 1170 (Box 91, Folder 2697)
  - Box 41, folder 1171 (Box 91, Folder 2698)
  - Box 41, folder 1172 (Box 91, Folder 2699)
  - Box 41, folder 1173 (Box 91, Folder 2700)
  - Box 41, folder 1174 (Box 91, Folder 2701)
  - Box 41, folder 1176 (Box 91, Folder 2702)
  - Box 41, folder 1177 (Box 91, Folder 2703)
  - Box 41, folder 1178 (Box 92, Folder 2704)
  - Box 41, folder 1179 (Box 92, Folder 2705)
  - Box 41, folder 1180 (Box 92, Folder 2706)
  - Box 41, folder 1181 (Box 92, Folder 2707)
  - Box 41, folder 1182 (Box 92, Folder 2708)
  - Box 41, folder 1183 (Box 92, Folder 2709)
  - Box 43, folder 1217 (Box 92, Folder 2710)
  - Box 43, folder 1218 (Box 92, Folder 2711)
  - Box 43, folder 1220 (Box 92, Folder 2712)
  - Box 43, folder 1226 (Box 92, Folder 2713)
  - Box 43, folder 1227 (Box 92, Folder 2714)
  - Box 43, folder 1230 (Box 92, Folder 2715)
  - Box 43, folder 1234 (Box 92, Folder 2716)
  - Box 43, folder 1235 (Box 92, Folder 2717)
  - Box 44, folder 1237 (Box 92, Folder 2718)
  - Box 44, folder 1238 (Box 92, Folder 2719)
  - Box 44, folder 1240 (Box 92, Folder 2720)
  - Box 44, folder 1241 (Box 92, Folder 2721)
  - Box 44, folder 1247 (Box 92, Folder 2722)
  - Box 44, folder 1248 (Box 92, Folder 2723)
  - Box 44, folder 1249 (Box 92, Folder 2724)